<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"
					xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

				<channel>

				<title>IIT UBF Events</title>

				<atom:link href="http://www.iitubf.org/events/eventsfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

				<description>Latest event information from iitubf.org</description>

				<link>http://www.iitubf.org/events/</link>
<item>

				<title>International Day of Prayer 2011</title>

				<description><![CDATA[Please join with us as we join with churches around the world to <b>"remember those in bonds"</b>  (Hebrews 13:3) on Nov. 13, the International Day of Prayer for the Persecuted Church (IDOP). Begun in 1996, IDOP is a day for intercessory prayer and citizen action on behalf of persecuted Christian communities worldwide. It is estimated that more than 100,000 churches, from more than 130 countries, have taken part in IDOP activities during this period.<br/><br/>

				We are planning to have <b>fasting prayer all day Sunday</b> and we would like to invite you to join with us for a special prayer session Sunday morning after our normal worship service in the Chapel. You are welcome to join our normal worship service which starts at 10AM and finishes about 11AM.]]></description>

				<link>/events/index.html?event_id=11</link>

				<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 19:19:00 -0700</pubDate>

				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.iitubf.org/events/index.html?event_id=11</guid>

				</item><item>

				<title>Coffee House Returns</title>

				<description><![CDATA[Free coffee and prayer as you prepare study.<br/><br/>
					Get a pick up as you study from the IIT Bible Club and IIT UBF as they serve coffee to and offer prayer for students. We'll be in the Galvin Library on October 16 from 2pm to 5pm. ]]></description>

				<link>/events/index.html?event_id=10</link>

				<pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2011 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate>

				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.iitubf.org/events/index.html?event_id=10</guid>

				</item>
				
				<item>

				<title>Christmas Worship Service 2010</title>

				<description><![CDATA["The virgin will conceive and give birth to a son, and they will call him Immanuel (which means 'God with us')" -Matthew 1:23<br/> 
This year's theme is <b>Jesus is Immanuel: God With Us</b>. Join us as we will remember and celebrate the birth of our Lord Jesus Christ, who is God with us. There will be a Christmas message, followed by drama, chorus, dance and fellowship. Email iitubf at gmail for more information. We would love for you to join us! ]]></description>

				<link>/events/index.html?event_id=9</link>

				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 22:17:00 -0700</pubDate>

				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.iitubf.org/events/index.html?event_id=9</guid>

				</item>
<item>

				<title>International Day of Prayer 2010</title>

				<description><![CDATA[Please join with us as we join with churches around the world to <b>"remember those in bonds"</b>  (Hebrews 13:3) on Nov. 14, the International Day of Prayer for the Persecuted Church (IDOP). Begun in 1996, IDOP is a day for intercessory prayer and citizen action on behalf of persecuted Christian communities worldwide. It is estimated that more than 100,000 churches, from more than 130 countries, have taken part in IDOP activities during this period.<br/><br/>

				We are planning to have <b>fasting prayer all day Sunday</b> and we would like to invite you to join with us for a special prayer session Sunday morning after our normal worship service in the Chapel. You are welcome to join our normal worship service which starts at 10AM and finishes about 11AM.]]></description>

				<link>/events/index.html?event_id=8</link>

				<pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 15:54:00 -0700</pubDate>

				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.iitubf.org/events/index.html?event_id=8</guid>

				</item>
<item>

				<title>Time Management</title>

				<description><![CDATA[The IIT Bible club is happy to host an outreach event on Christian Time Management. This presentation will be given by Dr. Alan Wolff from Northwestern University. He says, "We should be good stewards of one of the most precious things God gave us: time. There are so many demands on our time. How can we use our time most effectively to be the best God wants us to be? In this talk we will present practical concepts from a classic book and discuss their underlying Biblical principles."]]></description>

				<link>/events/index.html?event_id=7</link>

				<pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2010 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>

				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.iitubf.org/events/index.html?event_id=7</guid>

				</item>
<item>

				<title>The Kingdom of God is Near</title>

				<description><![CDATA[Join us for our Midwest Region Summer Conference in Peoria, IL on July 8 to 11. ]]></description>

				<link>/events/index.html?event_id=6</link>

				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>

				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.iitubf.org/events/index.html?event_id=6</guid>

				</item>
<item>

				<title>Coffee House</title>

				<description><![CDATA[Free coffee and prayer as you prepare for finals. 
Get a pick up as you study for finals from the IIT Bible Club and IIT UBF as they serve coffee to and offer prayer for students. We'll be in the Galvin Library on May 2 from 2pm to 5pm and on May 3 from 6pm to 9pm.  ]]></description>

				<link>/events/index.html?event_id=5</link>

				<pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate>

				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.iitubf.org/events/index.html?event_id=5</guid>

				</item>
<item>

				<title>Arise</title>

				<description><![CDATA[Join us for the 2010 Easter Retreat titled &quot;Arise&quot; on April 2 to 4 at Dickson Valley in Newark, IL.  At this year&#39;s retreat, we want to focus on how Jesus&#39; death and resurrection allow us to rise from our lives of sin and hopelessness.  There will be messages, Bible studies, and time to get to know God and your fellow Christians better. ]]></description>

				<link>/events/index.html?event_id=4</link>

				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate>

				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.iitubf.org/events/index.html?event_id=4</guid>

				</item>
<item>

				<title>Christmas Worship Service 2009</title>

				<description><![CDATA[&quot;But you, Bethlehem, in the land of Judah, are by no means least among the rulers of Judah; for out of you will come a ruler who will be the shepherd of my people Israel.&quot; -Matt 2:6 
This year's theme is &quot;A Shepherd for My People.&quot; Join us as we will remember and celebrate the birth of our Lord Jesus Christ. There will be a Christmas message, followed by drama, chorus, dance and fellowship. Email iitubf at gmail for more information. We would love for you to join us! ]]></description>

				<link>/events/index.html?event_id=3</link>

				<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2009 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>

				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.iitubf.org/events/index.html?event_id=3</guid>

				</item>
<item>

				<title>Triple Band Blowout 2009</title>

				<description><![CDATA[We will be participating in the 3rd annual UBF multi-campus outreach concert!  This year it will be held at the Triton College campus. Come listen and join in some great music performed by Triton UBF, West Loop UBF and IIT UBF!!  Let us know if you'd like a ride out there & back.  More detailed information to follow.
	<br /> 
	<br /> 
	Pictures from the <a href='http://www.iitubf.org/media/gallery.php?albumId=5240378633144743041&albumName=Triple+Band+Blowout'>2007 Outreach Concert</a> 
	<br /> 
	<br /> 
	Pictures from the <a href='http://www.iitubf.org/media/gallery.php?albumId=5251254390302504209&albumName=Rock+of+Our+Salvation'>2008 Outreach Concert</a> ]]></description>

				<link>/events/index.html?event_id=2</link>

				<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>

				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.iitubf.org/events/index.html?event_id=2</guid>

				</item>
<item>

				<title>IIT Student Resource Fair</title>

				<description><![CDATA[The IIT Bible Club will have a booth at the Student Org Fair where students can find out more about the organization and sign up to receive meeting and event notices.  Please come find us and stop by, we'd love to get to know you!]]></description>

				<link>/events/index.html?event_id=1</link>

				<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>

				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.iitubf.org/events/index.html?event_id=1</guid>

				</item>
</channel>

			</rss>